seafolly.com 2019-04-02

# Privacy Policy | Seafolly United States

Seafolly values your privacy

### What We Use Your Personal Information For

Seafolly keeps confidential all personally identifiable information you provide us.

If you register your details with us, or order a catalogue, your information allows us to communicate with you about our products, promotions and activities.

The information that you provide us through our website will be used to update our customer database. This information is for Seafolly’s internal use only, and is used for the purpose of customer communication.

If you purchase any of your products online, we will also use the information you provide us to process your order and its delivery to you.

### Accessing Your Information

We like to know that the personal information you provide us is accurate, complete and up to date. If you notice that your personal information is missing or incorrect, you can update your details online on our website.

So that we can continue to offer you great offers and promotion info, we give you the opportunity to say yes to being contacted by Seafolly. This is totally your choice and you can opt out of the future contact whenever you want.

If you would like your name deleted from the database please email shop@seafolly.com.au requesting deletion. You will be deleted from our database within 48 hours.

### Sharing Information with Third Parties

When we collect, hold and use your personal information, we do so primarily to sell and promote our product to you and to improve on the range of our offerings. For example; to learn of your likely preferences so that we may promote our goods and services to you in a way which may be of most interest to you; and to assist in investigating your complaints and enquiries.

We disclose personal information we collect for purposes which are incidental to the sale and promotion of our goods and services to you. For example, we may disclose your personal information within our group, to service providers who assist us in our day-to-day business operations and as part of buying or selling businesses.

We may collect, hold, use and disclose your personal information for other purposes which are within reasonable expectations. For example; your name (a possibly your suburb) if you win a Seafolly competition, or your name and postal address to organisations that assist us with customer communications.

When marketing to you, your personal information is only ever used or disclosed for Seafolly’s own purposes. You may opt out of our direct marketing to you. Our direct marketing materials will tell you how to do this.

### Deleting Information

We ensure that any personal information we no longer need is either destroyed or that you become permanently unidentifiable from the information.

### Cardholder account data

Seafolly does not store any cardholder data, all credit card payment services are secure and are handled by SecurePay.

### SECUREPAY SECURITY STANDARDS

We prioritise protecting your personal and order information and have created a secure online shopping environment . The focus of our security is centred around the safe processing and storage of sensitive personal Credit Card, Charge Card and Direct Entry information. PCI DSS (Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard) Compliance is a strict security standard the card schemes (Visa and MasterCard) have introduced globally to ensure personal information is properly protected. SecurePay holds the highest level of PCI DSS accreditation.

### Vectra Corporation

SecurePay’s Operations Network is audited on an ongoing basis by external auditors, namely Vectra Corporation, for the purpose of certifying compliance with PCI DSS. Ongoing network scans, a requirement of PCI DSS, are completed regularly and are performed by McAfee Secure.

The services that SecurePay is authorised to provide under PCI DSS include:

  * Authorisation Services
  * Clearing / Settlement Services
  * IPSP (e-Commerce)
  * Payment Gateway
  * Switch
  * Processing MOTO Transations
  * 3-D Secure Access Control Server

Please see [www.securepay.com.au/security_standards.html](http://www.securepay.com.au/security_standards.html) for more information.

### Copyright

Seafolly asserts copyright and all other intellectual rights in relation to the content of this Internet site and code used to create it, unless stated otherwise.

Seafolly also reserves copyright and all other intellectual property rights in relation to all of its documents and images appearing on or linked to this web site. Users of this website may download a single copy of these documents or images for their personal use only.

### Contact Us

For further information on Seafolly, or if you have any questions about the personal information we hold about you, why we hold it and how we use and disclose your information, please email [info@seafolly.com.au](mailto:info@seafolly.com.au) or call [+61 2 8339 8222](tel:+61-2-8339-8222).

More information on privacy legislation is available from the Federal Privacy Commissioner at [www.privacy.gov.au](http://www.privacy.gov.au/).
